Rohan

123 Somewhere Road, Niceville, FL

(555) 888-0000

gaurav@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

An MBA with 5 years of experience developing and managing marketing campaigns and specialized working knowledge of Google Analytics and AdWords, seeks the role of Social Media Marketing Manager with bnm Inc. to implement successful digital marketing campaigns and provide exceptional thought leadership.

SUMMARY OF SKILLS

Three years of specialized experience in SQL, ML, R, hive

Managed social media accounts for four businesses with yearly sales over \$500,000

Certified Digital Marketer 2016, Udemy

Received Employee of the Year Award at bnm Company 2018 and 2019

WORK EXPERIENCE

full stack web developer, ABC Company, Nashville, TN, 2017-2020

Built a 15k Facebook following and 20k Instagram following for new startup, increasing leads by 160%

Developed compelling CTAs for website and social media copy, producing a 60% increase in sales

Formulated Instagram strategy and collaborated with influencers in our market to promote topselling products, resulting in \$200,000 net sales in three months

Web developer, 123 Company, Austin, TX, 2014-2017

Team member for the design and development of new mobile application

Conducted A/B testing on paid Facebook and Instagram campaigns, resulting in a boost in conversion from 70% to 90%.

Implemented innovative SEO strategy to increase organic website traffic 200% in five months

EDUCATION

University of Michigan, 2006-2010

REFERENCES

Available upon request